Office of Student Services, School of Dental Medicine Records UA235
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Post Graduate files, 1948 -- 2018; UA235.002; 42.5 Linear Feet
  - Laprade, Andre J., 1988; UA235.002.062.00061 (Box 62)
  - Lara, Armando, 1976; UA235.002.062.00062 (Box 62)
  - Larder, Thomas, 1977; UA235.002.062.00063 (Box 62)
  - La Salvia, Joan N., 1999; UA235.002.062.00064 (Box 62)
  - LaScala, Nelson, 1959; UA235.002.062.00065 (Box 62)
  - Lashgari, Michael D., 1995; UA235.002.062.00066 (Box 62)
  - Laskou, Meletia, 1993; UA235.002.062.00067 (Box 62)
  - Latypoua, Kateryna, 2005; UA235.002.062.00068 (Box 62)
  - Lauder, Keith, 1975; UA235.002.062.00069 (Box 62)
  - Lavall, Michelle B., 1996; UA235.002.062.00070 (Box 62)
  - Lavalette, Robert W., 1949; UA235.002.062.00071 (Box 62)
  - Laverde, Mario Jiminez, 1965; UA235.002.062.00072 (Box 62)
  - Leaderman, Richard N., 1974; UA235.002.062.00073 (Box 62)
  - Leal, Enrique J., 1965; UA235.002.062.00074 (Box 62)
  - Leary, Joseph, 1977; UA235.002.062.00075 (Box 62)
  - LeBeller, Eric, 1988; UA235.002.063.00001 (Box 63)
  - Lee, Chien-Hung Jack, 1998; UA235.002.063.00002 (Box 63)
  - Lee, Brian B, 1995; UA235.002.063.00003 (Box 63)
  - Lee, Shandra C, 2003; UA235.002.063.00004 (Box 63)
  - Lee, Chao-Min, 1993; UA235.002.063.00005 (Box 63)
  - Lee, Hyunkyung Y, 1992; UA235.002.063.00006 (Box 63)
  - Lee, James S, 1987; UA235.002.063.00007 (Box 63)
  - Lee, John H, 2001; UA235.002.063.00008 (Box 63)
  - Lee, Norman, 2003; UA235.002.063.00009 (Box 63)
  - Lee, Richard, 1984; UA235.002.063.00010 (Box 63)
  - Leelawat, Chilaporn, 1982; UA235.002.063.00011 (Box 63)
  - Lefebvre, Richard F, 1961; UA235.002.063.00012 (Box 63)
  - Legg, William J, 1963; UA235.002.063.00013 (Box 63)
  - Leiber, Gerald B, 1971; UA235.002.063.00014 (Box 63)
  - Liebman, mayer, 1970; UA235.002.063.00015 (Box 63)
  - Leibowitz, Henry, 1963; UA235.002.063.00016 (Box 63)
  - Leichrer, Samuel F, 1967; UA235.002.063.00017 (Box 63)
  - Leiderman, Richard S, 1974; UA235.002.063.00018 (Box 63)
  - Leikin, Robert A, 1957; UA235.002.063.00019 (Box 63)
  - Lem, John, 1982; UA235.002.063.00020 (Box 63)
  - Lemense, Joseph, 1950; UA235.002.063.00021 (Box 63)
  - Lemire, Donald, 1994; UA235.002.063.00022 (Box 63)
  - Leonard, Jeffrey, 1996; UA235.002.063.00023 (Box 63)
  - Leong, Denise, 2003; UA235.002.063.00024 (Box 63)
  - Leonard, Thomas george, 1970; UA235.002.063.00025 (Box 63)
  - Lepore, Michael F, 1983; UA235.002.063.00026 (Box 63)
  - Less, William C, 1960; UA235.002.063.00027 (Box 63)
  - Letzer, Gerald M, 1965; UA235.002.063.00028 (Box 63)
  - Levi, Paula, Jr, 1969; UA235.002.063.00029 (Box 63)
  - Levick, Alan Louis, 1969; UA235.002.063.00030 (Box 63)
    Open for research.
  - Levin, Joel, 1964; UA235.002.063.00031 (Box 63)
  - Levin, Martin A, 1962; UA235.002.063.00032 (Box 63)
  - Levine, Nolem Leib, 1970; UA235.002.063.00033 (Box 63)
  - Levine, Robert B, 1969; UA235.002.063.00034 (Box 63)
  - Levinson, Gordon Arnold, 1969; UA235.002.063.00035 (Box 63)
  - Levy, Paul F, 1973; UA235.002.063.00036 (Box 63)
  - Lewis, Budner, 1948; UA235.002.063.00037 (Box 63)
  - Liao, Wei-Ying, 1988; UA235.002.063.00038 (Box 63)
  - Librizzi, Theodore, 1982; UA235.002.063.00039 (Box 63)
  - Lichter, Harvey A, 1960; UA235.002.063.00040 (Box 63)
  - Licht, Raymond S, 1953; UA235.002.063.00041 (Box 63)
  - Light, Robert B, 1983; UA235.002.063.00042 (Box 63)
  - Lignini, Cinzia, 1989; UA235.002.063.00043 (Box 63)
  - Likhari, Vikram, 2006; UA235.002.063.00044 (Box 63)
  - Lim, Suns-Sun, 2002; UA235.002.063.00045 (Box 63)
  - Lim, Toh-Woon, 1974; UA235.002.063.00046 (Box 63)
  - Lincoln, Robert E, 1989; UA235.002.063.00047 (Box 63)
  - Lin, Heng-Sheng, 1988; UA235.002.063.00048 (Box 63)
  - Lin, Jenn-Yih, 1999; UA235.002.063.00049 (Box 63)
  - Lin, Jerry Hong-I, 1986; UA235.002.063.00050 (Box 63)
  - Lin, Ming-Shi, 1991; UA235.002.063.00051 (Box 63)
  - Lin, Ming-Shi, 1984; UA235.002.063.00052 (Box 63)
  - Lin, Shiao-Yu, 1993; UA235.002.063.00053 (Box 63)
  - Lin, Synsyn Y, 2000; UA235.002.063.00054 (Box 63)
  - Lin, Yu-Heng, 1991; UA235.002.063.00055 (Box 63)
  - Lindquist, N. Rich, 1976; UA235.002.063.00056 (Box 63)
  - Linjawi, Amal, 1999; UA235.002.063.00057 (Box 63)
  - Lipski, Miriam H, 1949; UA235.002.063.00058 (Box 63)
  - Lipski, Matthew A, 1969; UA235.002.063.00059 (Box 63)
  - Lipton, Lawrence, 1974; UA235.002.063.00060 (Box 63)
  - Lipton, Shayne, 1979; UA235.002.063.00061 (Box 63)
  - Liss, Michael S, 1988; UA235.002.063.00062 (Box 63)
  - Litchen, Michael, 1968; UA235.002.063.00063 (Box 63)
  - Litsas, George, 1995; UA235.002.063.00064 (Box 63)
  - Livanos, Gregory, 1992; UA235.002.063.00065 (Box 63)
  - Lobene, Ralph, 1962; UA235.002.063.00066 (Box 63)
  - Lobo Lobo, Silvia, 2007; UA235.002.063.00067 (Box 63)
  - Loeffler, Terry C, 1974; UA235.002.063.00068 (Box 63)
  - Loewenthal, Bernard, 1968; UA235.002.063.00069 (Box 63)
  - Loftus, Edward R, 1960; UA235.002.063.00070 (Box 63)
  - Lopez, Mercedes, 1980; UA235.002.063.00071 (Box 63)
  - Lotfizadeh, Hassan, 1976; UA235.002.063.00072 (Box 63)
  - Hadjinikolaou, Loukia S, 1995; UA235.002.064.00001 (Box 64)
  - Lowery, Michael, 2004; UA235.002.064.00002 (Box 64)
  - Lozano, Ana Marie, 1983; UA235.002.064.00003 (Box 64)
  - Lucas, John G, 1954; UA235.002.064.00004 (Box 64)
  - Luddington, Dean F, 1962; UA235.002.064.00005 (Box 64)
  - Luddington, Richard D, 1987; UA235.002.064.00006 (Box 64)
  - Lung, Darryl J, 1986; UA235.002.064.00007 (Box 64)
  - Lyon, Stephen M, 1990; UA235.002.064.00008 (Box 64)
  - Lyons, Edward J., Jr, 1960; UA235.002.064.00009 (Box 64)
  - Lytinas, Michail, 1998; UA235.002.064.00010 (Box 64)
  - MacMillan, Anthony, 1970; UA235.002.064.00011 (Box 64)
  - Madan, Rafael, 1952; UA235.002.064.00012 (Box 64)
  - Maeng, Myong, 2002; UA235.002.064.00013 (Box 64)
  - Maghrabi, Abdulhmaid, 1992; UA235.002.064.00014 (Box 64)
  - Magurno, Maria A, 1999; UA235.002.064.00015 (Box 64)
  - Mahdavi, Peiman, 1992; UA235.002.064.00016 (Box 64)
  - Mailander, Gary D, 1965; UA235.002.064.00017 (Box 64)
  - Malagodi, Ralph, 1979; UA235.002.064.00018 (Box 64)
  - Mallek, Henry M, 1973; UA235.002.064.00019 (Box 64)
  - Mallouh, Abboud, 1995; UA235.002.064.00020 (Box 64)
  - Malloy, John C, 1994; UA235.002.064.00021 (Box 64)
  - Maloff, Arnold, 1979; UA235.002.064.00022 (Box 64)
  - Maloff, Jeffrey, 1984; UA235.002.064.00023 (Box 64)
  - Maloney, Bernard, 1974; UA235.002.064.00024 (Box 64)
  - Maloney, tracy, 1993; UA235.002.064.00025 (Box 64)
  - Maloney, Philip L, 1964; UA235.002.064.00026 (Box 64)
  - Maloney, Tracy E, 1991; UA235.002.064.00027 (Box 64)
  - Malouf, Shibley, 1960; UA235.002.064.00028 (Box 64)
  - Mancini, Kevin J, 1999; UA235.002.064.00029 (Box 64)
  - Mandalenakis, Constantin, 1981; UA235.002.064.00030 (Box 64)
  - Maness, William L, 1971; UA235.002.064.00031 (Box 64)
  - Maness, William, 1974; UA235.002.064.00032 (Box 64)
  - Manickas, Agisilaos P, 1980; UA235.002.064.00033 (Box 64)
  - Mann, Arnold, 1988; UA235.002.064.00034 (Box 64)
  - Manning, Beatrice, 1972; UA235.002.064.00035 (Box 64)
  - Manson, Julius, 1958; UA235.002.064.00036 (Box 64)
  - Mansour, Frederick M, 1958; UA235.002.064.00037 (Box 64)
  - Mansour, Philip M, 1988; UA235.002.064.00038 (Box 64)
  - Manthos, Laurie, 1987; UA235.002.064.00039 (Box 64)
  - Manwaring, Jeremy, 2002; UA235.002.064.00040 (Box 64)
  - Mao, Chhy, 2004; UA235.002.064.00041 (Box 64)
  - Marchetto, John J, 1984; UA235.002.064.00042 (Box 64)
  - Marfino, Michael, 1960; UA235.002.064.00043 (Box 64)
  - Mariano, Vincent J, 1982; UA235.002.064.00044 (Box 64)
  - Marino, Joseph A, 1988; UA235.002.064.00045 (Box 64)
  - Marino, Paul A, 1961; UA235.002.064.00046 (Box 64)
  - Markarian, Shant, 1979; UA235.002.064.00047 (Box 64)
  - Marks, Lawrence, 1986; UA235.002.064.00048 (Box 64)
  - Marks, Robert m, 1961; UA235.002.064.00049 (Box 64)
  - Marks, Robert T, 1969; UA235.002.064.00050 (Box 64)
  - Marks, Sandy, 1979; UA235.002.064.00051 (Box 64)
  - Marranzini, Maria G, 2001; UA235.002.064.00052 (Box 64)
  - Marti, Alejandro Mendez, 1960; UA235.002.064.00053 (Box 64)
  - Martin, Clark A, 1983; UA235.002.064.00054 (Box 64)
  - Martinez, James E, 1995; UA235.002.064.00055 (Box 64)
  - Marynoik, George, 1981; UA235.002.064.00056 (Box 64)
  - Masayanavich, Rosalynn, 1981; UA235.002.064.00057 (Box 64)
  - Massaro, Christa E, 2004; UA235.002.064.00058 (Box 64)
  - Mata, Jaime, 1982; UA235.002.064.00059 (Box 64)
  - Matsunaga, raymond, 1960; UA235.002.064.00060 (Box 64)
  - Matza, Barry I, 1974; UA235.002.064.00061 (Box 64)
  - Maurer, Suanne, 1995; UA235.002.064.00062 (Box 64)
  - Mautner, Robert, 1981; UA235.002.064.00063 (Box 64)
  - Maybury, Joseph, 1962; UA235.002.064.00064 (Box 64)
  - Mayer, Mattias, 1997; UA235.002.064.00065 (Box 64)
  - Mazzocco, Domenic, 1989; UA235.002.064.00066 (Box 64)
  - Mazzocco, Fabio, 2004; UA235.002.064.00067 (Box 64)
  - McCabe, Bernard, 1965; UA235.002.064.00068 (Box 64)
  - McCall, Carol A, 1984; UA235.002.064.00069 (Box 64)
  - McFee, Conrad, 1968; UA235.002.064.00070 (Box 64)
  - McGillicuddy, Thomas, 1981; UA235.002.064.00071 (Box 64)
  - McGowan, Charles, 1960; UA235.002.064.00072 (Box 64)
  - McInturff, Allen, 1955; UA235.002.064.00073 (Box 64)
  - McKenna, Christine, E, 1987; UA235.002.064.00074 (Box 64)
  - McKenna, Paul, 1980; UA235.002.064.00075 (Box 64)
  - McKenna, Stephen, 1988; UA235.002.064.00076 (Box 64)
  - McLaughlin, Brendan, 2000; UA235.002.064.00077 (Box 64)
  - McLaughlin, Craig, 1986; UA235.002.064.00078 (Box 64)
  - McLaughlin, Stephen, 1978; UA235.002.064.00079 (Box 64)
  - McLees, James K, 1969; UA235.002.064.00080 (Box 64)
  - McNamara, Francis, 1967; UA235.002.064.00081 (Box 64)
  - McQuinn, Daniel T., 1993; UA235.002.065.00001 (Box 65)
  - McSweeney, Timothy M., 1997; UA235.002.065.00002 (Box 65)
  - Megarbane, Jean-Marie, 1979; UA235.002.065.00003 (Box 65)
  - Megas, Takis, 1983; UA235.002.065.00004 (Box 65)
  - Mehlman, Raymond F., 1985; UA235.002.065.00005 (Box 65)
  - Mehta, Fali, 1949; UA235.002.065.00006 (Box 65)
  - Mehta, Naushrwan R., 1969; UA235.002.065.00007 (Box 65)
  - Mehta, Rustom F., 1989; UA235.002.065.00008 (Box 65)
  - Meizner, Walter, 1982; UA235.002.065.00009 (Box 65)
  - Meline, Samuel, 1962; UA235.002.065.00010 (Box 65)
  - Meliou, Aikaterini A., 1997; UA235.002.065.00011 (Box 65)
  - Melis, Marcello, 1998; UA235.002.065.00012 (Box 65)
  - Melling, John, 1979; UA235.002.065.00013 (Box 65)
  - Mendeloff, Ernest, 1955; UA235.002.065.00014 (Box 65)
  - Mendez, Zuzana, 1996; UA235.002.065.00015 (Box 65)
  - Mendoza, Carlos, 1961; UA235.002.065.00016 (Box 65)
  - Medoza, Cesar, 1975; UA235.002.065.00017 (Box 65)
  - Merlet, Yves, 1976; UA235.002.065.00018 (Box 65)
  - Merrill, Ralph George, 1959; UA235.002.065.00019 (Box 65)
  - Mesgarzadeh, Abolhassan, 1966; UA235.002.065.00020 (Box 65)
  - Mesrobian, Armen, 1977; UA235.002.065.00021 (Box 65)
  - Methenitou, Sotiria, 1986; UA235.002.065.00022 (Box 65)
  - Metzger, Alan, 1976; UA235.002.065.00023 (Box 65)
  - Meyer, Marychris, 1994; UA235.002.065.00024 (Box 65)
  - Mezani, Hocine, 1981; UA235.002.065.00025 (Box 65)
  - Micellotti, Anthony, 1959; UA235.002.065.00026 (Box 65)
  - Michael, Carmy, 1996; UA235.002.065.00027 (Box 65)
  - Michel, Thomas, 1983; UA235.002.065.00028 (Box 65)
  - Mihalakis, Konstadinos, 1990; UA235.002.065.00029 (Box 65)
  - Miller, Edward, 1956; UA235.002.065.00030 (Box 65)
  - Miller, Jerald, 1959; UA235.002.065.00031 (Box 65)
  - Miller, Richard W., 1996; UA235.002.065.00032 (Box 65)
  - Miller, Richard Wheaton, 1972; UA235.002.065.00033 (Box 65)
  - Miller, Stanley R., 1972; UA235.002.065.00034 (Box 65)
  - Millstein, Philip, 1967; UA235.002.065.00035 (Box 65)
  - Milyani, Mohammed S.M., 1992; UA235.002.065.00036 (Box 65)
  - Mina, Polina A., 1999; UA235.002.065.00037 (Box 65)
  - Minukhim, Olga, 2004; UA235.002.065.00038 (Box 65)
  - Mirchandani, Shalini, 1990; UA235.002.065.00039 (Box 65)
  - Mirdad, Amani, 2001; UA235.002.065.00040 (Box 65)
  - Mana, Mirfendereski, 2004; UA235.002.065.00041 (Box 65)
  - Mirghassemi, Mahshid, 2001; UA235.002.065.00042 (Box 65)
  - Mirza, Firoze Dara, 1957; UA235.002.065.00043 (Box 65)
  - Missert, William (1), 1998; UA235.002.065.00044 (Box 65)
  - Missert, William (2), 1997; UA235.002.065.00045 (Box 65)
  - Moghaddas, Hamid, 1976; UA235.002.065.00046 (Box 65)
  - Mohajeri, M.R., 1976; UA235.002.065.00047 (Box 65)
  - Mohajeri, Mohamed, 1975; UA235.002.065.00048 (Box 65)
  - Mohammed, Clive Imran, 1949; UA235.002.065.00049 (Box 65)
  - Mohammadi, Mohammad, 1977; UA235.002.065.00050 (Box 65)
  - Moini, Mohammad, 1973; UA235.002.065.00051 (Box 65)
  - Mokeem, Sameer Abdullah, 1991; UA235.002.065.00052 (Box 65)
  - Moll, Douglas H., 1989; UA235.002.065.00053 (Box 65)
  - Molloy, Daniel J., 1987; UA235.002.065.00054 (Box 65)
  - Molloy, Philip, 1965; UA235.002.065.00055 (Box 65)
  - Monastersky, Benson, 1966; UA235.002.065.00056 (Box 65)
  - Monmtaheni, Moshen, 1988; UA235.002.065.00057 (Box 65)
  - Montemurno, Thomas, 2005; UA235.002.065.00058 (Box 65)
  - Montes, Manuel, 1980; UA235.002.065.00059 (Box 65)
  - Montesani, Luigi, 1984; UA235.002.065.00060 (Box 65)
  - Montesani, Luigi, 1982; UA235.002.065.00061 (Box 65)
  - Montillo, Alfonso G., 1993; UA235.002.065.00062 (Box 65)
  - Moore, James, 2001; UA235.002.065.00063 (Box 65)
  - Mora, Clodomiro, 1956; UA235.002.065.00064 (Box 65)
  - Moreau, John, 1962; UA235.002.066.00001 (Box 66)
  - Morelli, Joseph, 1989; UA235.002.066.00002 (Box 66)
  - Morin, Edward Marshall, 1960; UA235.002.066.00003 (Box 66)
  - Morrison, Stephen K, 1985; UA235.002.066.00004 (Box 66)
  - Moroi, Hidetada, 1992; UA235.002.066.00005 (Box 66)
  - Morrison, Thaddeus, 1951; UA235.002.066.00006 (Box 66)
  - Mosadomi, Hezekiah, 1974; UA235.002.066.00007 (Box 66)
  - Moshiri, Farhad, 1975; UA235.002.066.00008 (Box 66)
  - Moshirfar, Catherine, 2002; UA235.002.066.00009 (Box 66)
  - Moskowitz, Gary, 1963; UA235.002.066.00010 (Box 66)
  - Moser, Charles R, 1982; UA235.002.066.00011 (Box 66)
  - Moutos, Minelaos, G, 1969; UA235.002.066.00012 (Box 66)
  - Moyel, Robert, 1955; UA235.002.066.00013 (Box 66)
  - Moynihan, Frederick, 1950; UA235.002.066.00014 (Box 66)
  - Moynihan, Robert, 1958; UA235.002.066.00015 (Box 66)
  - Parsons, Jeffrey R, 1969; UA235.002.066.00016 (Box 66)
  - Mullane, Phillip, 1966; UA235.002.066.00017 (Box 66)
  - Mulvihill, Thomas K, 1969; UA235.002.066.00018 (Box 66)
  - Muneeb, Sarah, 2000; UA235.002.066.00019 (Box 66)
  - Munera, Jose Leon, 1950; UA235.002.066.00020 (Box 66)
  - Murnane, Thomas, 1968; UA235.002.066.00021 (Box 66)
  - Murat, Andre, 1982; UA235.002.066.00022 (Box 66)
  - Murphy, Daniel, 1950; UA235.002.066.00023 (Box 66)
  - Murphy, James, 1974; UA235.002.066.00024 (Box 66)
  - Murphy, John, 1969; UA235.002.066.00025 (Box 66)
  - Myers, Donald, 1959; UA235.002.066.00026 (Box 66)
  - Myones, William, 1975; UA235.002.066.00027 (Box 66)
  - Nachtrab, Herbert R, 1981; UA235.002.066.00028 (Box 66)
  - Nadeau, James, 1969; UA235.002.066.00029 (Box 66)
  - Naghieh, Taraneh, 1992; UA235.002.066.00030 (Box 66)
  - Nahas, Ihsan, 1963; UA235.002.066.00031 (Box 66)
  - Naidu, Kistama, 2002; UA235.002.066.00032 (Box 66)
  - Nakayama, Yoshinari, 1977; UA235.002.066.00033 (Box 66)
  - Nareg-Olivier, Alexandrian O, 1997; UA235.002.066.00034 (Box 66)
  - Narula, Minakshi, 1994; UA235.002.066.00035 (Box 66)
  - Nathanson, Irving, 1950; UA235.002.066.00036 (Box 66)
  - Hajiseyedjavadi, Navid, 2004; UA235.002.066.00037 (Box 66)
  - Neagu, Mihaela, 2001; UA235.002.066.00038 (Box 66)
  - Neal, Michael D, 1996; UA235.002.066.00039 (Box 66)
  - Neimark, Lawrence, 1967; UA235.002.066.00040 (Box 66)
  - Nelson, Eugene, 1949; UA235.002.066.00041 (Box 66)
  - Nelson, Maurice, 1968; UA235.002.066.00042 (Box 66)
  - Nelson, Robert, 1966; UA235.002.066.00043 (Box 66)
  - Nemarich, Alfred N, 1969; UA235.002.066.00044 (Box 66)
  - Nersasian, Robert, 1969; UA235.002.066.00045 (Box 66)
  - Neville, Thomas Francis, 1964; UA235.002.066.00046 (Box 66)
  - Newman, George, 1964; UA235.002.066.00047 (Box 66)
  - Newman, Frank, 2003; UA235.002.066.00048 (Box 66)
  - Nezi, Eleni, 1985; UA235.002.066.00049 (Box 66)
  - Ng, Chung Shun, 1964; UA235.002.066.00050 (Box 66)
  - Nguyen, Minh, 2002; UA235.002.066.00051 (Box 66)
  - Nguyen, Timothy, 1992; UA235.002.066.00052 (Box 66)
  - Nguyen, Thu-Trinh N, 1999; UA235.002.066.00053 (Box 66)
  - Nikaido, Masahiko, 1993; UA235.002.066.00054 (Box 66)
  - Niakiani, Roya, 1995; UA235.002.066.00055 (Box 66)
  - Nicolas, George R, 1993; UA235.002.066.00056 (Box 66)
  - Ninika, Anastassia J, 1985; UA235.002.066.00057 (Box 66)
  - Niukian, Khadik, 1969; UA235.002.066.00058 (Box 66)
  - Noel, Suzanne, 1980; UA235.002.066.00059 (Box 66)
  - Nizel, Abraham E, 1950; UA235.002.066.00060 (Box 66)
  - Nooh, Nasser, 1990; UA235.002.066.00061 (Box 66)
  - Novel, Alexandra, 1992; UA235.002.066.00062 (Box 66)
  - Norris, Lonnie, 1979; UA235.002.066.00063 (Box 66)
  - Norskey, Alexander, 1977; UA235.002.066.00064 (Box 66)
  - Nosworthy, Donald G, 1970; UA235.002.066.00065 (Box 66)
  - Novack, Neal M, 1991; UA235.002.066.00066 (Box 66)
  - O'Brien, Thomas J, 1959; UA235.002.066.00067 (Box 66)
  - O'Donnell, James C, 1960; UA235.002.066.00068 (Box 66)
  - O'Donnell, Joseph, 1973; UA235.002.066.00069 (Box 66)
  - O'Donnell, William F, 1954; UA235.002.066.00070 (Box 66)
  - O'Grady, Dennis, 1991; UA235.002.066.00071 (Box 66)
  - O'Grady, Alan Michael, 1972; UA235.002.066.00072 (Box 66)
  - O'Leary, James M, 1986; UA235.002.066.00073 (Box 66)
  - Oles-Karasko, Anita, 2001; UA235.002.066.00074 (Box 66)
  - Olli, Edward, 1989; UA235.002.066.00075 (Box 66)
  - Olivieri, Francesco, 1992; UA235.002.066.00076 (Box 66)
  - O'Malley, John E., 1958; UA235.002.067.00001 (Box 67)
  - Omerovic, Mateo Papic, 1948; UA235.002.067.00002 (Box 67)
  - O'Neill, Rory, 1978; UA235.002.067.00003 (Box 67)
  - Oreadi, Armando, 1974; UA235.002.067.00004 (Box 67)
  - Ormaechea, Maria B., 1992; UA235.002.067.00005 (Box 67)
  - Ortiz, Jan, 2005; UA235.002.067.00006 (Box 67)
  - Orphanos, Ernest S., 1992; UA235.002.067.00007 (Box 67)
  - Ortiz-Yunes, Eric A., 1994; UA235.002.067.00008 (Box 67)
  - O'Shea, Kevin E., 1990; UA235.002.067.00009 (Box 67)
  - O'Shea, Kevin, 1992; UA235.002.067.00010 (Box 67)
  - Osher, Alfred, 1959; UA235.002.067.00011 (Box 67)
  - Ostaski, William, 1961; UA235.002.067.00012 (Box 67)
  - Othon, Leander G., 1969; UA235.002.067.00013 (Box 67)
  - Ouhayoun, Jean P., 1969; UA235.002.067.00014 (Box 67)
  - Ouzounian, Soucen, 1957; UA235.002.067.00015 (Box 67)
  - Owings, Jerry R., 1966; UA235.002.067.00016 (Box 67)
  - Pabon, Paola M., 2003; UA235.002.067.00017 (Box 67)
  - Pack, Philip, 1980; UA235.002.067.00018 (Box 67)
  - Packman, Harold J., 1967; UA235.002.067.00019 (Box 67)
  - Padamsee, Murad, 1995; UA235.002.067.00020 (Box 67)
  - Padamsee, Murad N., 1984; UA235.002.067.00021 (Box 67)
  - Paehler, Bettina, 2004; UA235.002.067.00022 (Box 67)
  - Pallanca, Claude, 1958; UA235.002.067.00023 (Box 67)
  - Palau, Jorge Alberto, 1969; UA235.002.067.00024 (Box 67)
  - Paley, Stephen, 1961; UA235.002.067.00025 (Box 67)
  - Palicoca, Charles A., 1963; UA235.002.067.00026 (Box 67)
  - Pan, Alan, 2004; UA235.002.067.00027 (Box 67)
  - Panopoulos, D., 1965; UA235.002.067.00028 (Box 67)
  - Pantazis, Nickos (1), 1992; UA235.002.067.00029 (Box 67)
  - Pantazis, Nickos (2), 1989; UA235.002.067.00030 (Box 67)
  - Papadogeorgaki, Anna, 1987; UA235.002.067.00031 (Box 67)
  - Beldekas, Maria, 1982; UA235.002.067.00032 (Box 67)
  - Papadopoulos, William, 1989; UA235.002.067.00033 (Box 67)
  - Papageorge (Beldekas), Maria (1), 1982; UA235.002.067.00034 (Box 67)
  - Papageorge (Beldekas), Maria B. (2), 1987; UA235.002.067.00035 (Box 67)
  - Papageorgiou, Athanasios, 1990; UA235.002.067.00036 (Box 67)
  - Papaioannou, Orsalia, 1980; UA235.002.067.00037 (Box 67)
  - Papaspyrou, Helen, 1988; UA235.002.067.00038 (Box 67)
  - Papastavropoulos, C., 1986; UA235.002.067.00039 (Box 67)
  - Papageorgiou, Demetris V., 1991; UA235.002.067.00040 (Box 67)
  - Papaioannou, Angeliki A., 1995; UA235.002.067.00041 (Box 67)
  - Papaioannou, Constantinos A., 1998; UA235.002.067.00042 (Box 67)
  - Papathanassiou, Alkaterini, 1996; UA235.002.067.00043 (Box 67)
  - Papantoniou, Eleni, 1999; UA235.002.067.00044 (Box 67)
  - Pappas, Karen, 1985; UA235.002.067.00045 (Box 67)
  - Pappas, Pamela, 1982; UA235.002.067.00046 (Box 67)
  - Parma, Katri Sabine, 1949; UA235.002.067.00047 (Box 67)
  - Parashis, Andreas O., 1983; UA235.002.067.00048 (Box 67)
  - Paraskevopoulou, Ekaterini H., 1991; UA235.002.067.00049 (Box 67)
  - Park, Hye Yang, 2003; UA235.002.067.00050 (Box 67)
  - Passamonti, Gino, 1972; UA235.002.067.00051 (Box 67)
  - Passloff, Robert W., 1988; UA235.002.067.00052 (Box 67)
  - Patel, Marzban G., 1969; UA235.002.067.00053 (Box 67)
  - Patel, Virendra, 1953; UA235.002.067.00054 (Box 67)
  - Patterson, Elmer, 1966; UA235.002.067.00055 (Box 67)
  - Patterson, Gerald, 1977; UA235.002.067.00056 (Box 67)
  - Pearce, Robert L., 1953; UA235.002.067.00057 (Box 67)
  - Pearlson, Stanley, 1964; UA235.002.067.00058 (Box 67)
  - Pechak, Jochen P., 1996; UA235.002.067.00059 (Box 67)
  - Pavlidou, Sofia, 2003; UA235.002.067.00060 (Box 67)
  - Pavlo, John A., 1998; UA235.002.067.00061 (Box 67)
  - Payne, John H., 1996; UA235.002.067.00062 (Box 67)
  - Pedeutour, Pierre, 1997; UA235.002.067.00063 (Box 67)
  - Pellecchia, Roberto, 2000; UA235.002.067.00064 (Box 67)
  - Pendergast, William, 1981; UA235.002.067.00065 (Box 67)
  - Peikin, Alan J., 1962; UA235.002.067.00066 (Box 67)
  - Pelletier, James L., 1987; UA235.002.067.00067 (Box 67)
  - Pentz, Donald O., 1966; UA235.002.067.00068 (Box 67)
  - Perez, Ana, 1977; UA235.002.067.00069 (Box 67)
  - Perim, Stewart I., 1988; UA235.002.067.00070 (Box 67)
  - Perkins, Robert E.L., 1954; UA235.002.067.00071 (Box 67)
  - Perlitsh, Rachel A., 1992; UA235.002.067.00072 (Box 67)
  - Perlitsch, Max J., 1964; UA235.002.067.00073 (Box 67)
  - Perlmutter, Carl J., 1968; UA235.002.067.00074 (Box 67)
  - Perry, Ronald D., 1994; UA235.002.067.00075 (Box 67)
  - Pesce, Louis, 2005; UA235.002.067.00076 (Box 67)
  - Petcharanond, Manivara, 1996; UA235.002.067.00077 (Box 67)
  - Petersen, Arlon M., 1985; UA235.002.067.00078 (Box 67)
  - Peterson, Barret G., 1986; UA235.002.067.00079 (Box 67)
  - Peterson, Carlton Hall, 1953; UA235.002.067.00080 (Box 67)
  - Petralis, Richard, 1963; UA235.002.067.00081 (Box 67)
  - Petridis, Charalampos, 1994; UA235.002.068.00001 (Box 68)
  - Pezeshkian, Ahmad, 1980; UA235.002.068.00002 (Box 68)
  - Phillippas, Gerassimos, 1979; UA235.002.068.00003 (Box 68)
  - Phillips, Homer, 1968; UA235.002.068.00004 (Box 68)
  - Phillis, Hugh, 1981; UA235.002.068.00005 (Box 68)
  - Piazzini, Lidia, 1991; UA235.002.068.00006 (Box 68)
  - Piazzini, Francesca, 1993; UA235.002.068.00007 (Box 68)
  - Pick, Clarice K, 1987; UA235.002.068.00008 (Box 68)
  - Pier, Mauncio, 1982; UA235.002.068.00009 (Box 68)
  - Pierce, Edward, 1951; UA235.002.068.00010 (Box 68)
  - Piedra, Isabella, 1992; UA235.002.068.00011 (Box 68)
  - Pinella, Maria, 1989 -- 1991; UA235.002.068.00071; 2 Folder(s) (Box 68)
  - Pingree, William, 1965; UA235.002.068.00012 (Box 68)
  - Piroshaw, Noshir, 1954; UA235.002.068.00013 (Box 68)
  - Pissiottis, Arairis, 1982; UA235.002.068.00014 (Box 68)
  - Pistiola, Loukia, 1990; UA235.002.068.00015 (Box 68)
  - Pittaway, John A, 1995; UA235.002.068.00016 (Box 68)
  - Pitzi, Robert F, 1974; UA235.002.068.00017 (Box 68)
  - Piyapinyo, Sirinporn, 1997; UA235.002.068.00018 (Box 68)
  - Plourde, Susan M, 1988; UA235.002.068.00019 (Box 68)
  - Pocharski, Louis, 1958; UA235.002.068.00020 (Box 68)
  - Pollaccia, Nino D, 2002; UA235.002.068.00021 (Box 68)
  - Podlin, Bernard, 1980; UA235.002.068.00022 (Box 68)
  - Poor, Williard, 1955; UA235.002.068.00023 (Box 68)